{
    "subject": "resource/Abidemi_Sanusi",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Lagos",
    "human_readable": "Abidemi Sanusi was born in Lagos.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9284272193908691,
            "question": "Where was Abidemi Sanusi born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4574580192565918,
            "question": "Is Abidemi Sanusi a public figure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25844061374664307,
            "question": "What country is Lagos located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20281416177749634,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Lagos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19952546060085297,
            "question": "What is Lagos known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17115618288516998,
            "question": "What language is commonly spoken in Lagos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11424173414707184,
            "question": "What is the history of Lagos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10723074525594711,
            "question": "Is Lagos a coastal city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0955028310418129,
            "question": "What are some popular tourist destinations in Lagos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08275701105594635,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Lagos?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Abidemi Sanusi was born in Lagos.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8740_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular tourist destinations in Lagos?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8740_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Lagos a coastal city?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8740_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the history of Lagos?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8740_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8740_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8740_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8740_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8740_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8740_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8740_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8740_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8740_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8740_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8740_71.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Abidemi Sanusi was born in Lagos, Nigeria. This can be inferred from multiple sources, including file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8740/re-ranker-msmarco/21.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8740/re-ranker-msmarco/33.txt, which both mention that Abidemi Sanusi was born in Lagos, Nigeria."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis answer is derived from the context provided, where multiple documents mention that \"Abidemi Sanusi was born in Lagos, Nigeria.\" Therefore, the statement \"Abidemi Sanusi was born in Lagos\" is supported by the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}